<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Mental Health Stories</title>
    <link>https://mentalhealthstories.nl/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Mental Health Stories</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2024 </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:59:16 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mentalhealthstories.nl/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Story #1</title>
      <link>https://mentalhealthstories.nl/posts/story_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:59:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mentalhealthstories.nl/posts/story_1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After years and years of abuse, I started to get therapy, The therapy helped for a while, but deep deep within, I still feel the rage and pent up anger, sadness and abuse, I have had times where I lay in bed, wondering where it went wrong, I wonder why it happened, how it happened, why the abuser is still free.
I sometimes have bursts of sadness and anger where I am practically unspeakable to, I go up to my room, cry, and after a fair amount of time, I start talking to people again.
I often have periods of time where I dont really talk to people I talk to a lot, these periods can range from a week to 5 months, I really dont enjoy them.
I feel very lonely from time to time, like I am not heard, like my speech has been taken away, like my vocal chords have been stripped from me, I often feel if as I am a ghost.
Whenever I look in the mirror, I dont think &amp;ldquo;Oh lala what a handsome fella we got over here!&amp;rdquo; I more so think like:&amp;ldquo;hmm, not much to work with&amp;rdquo;. I dont like myself, I dont like thinking about myself, I see myself as not that good of a human being, someone who doesnt deserve the things he has got. my self esteem is very low, at least, I think it is when I compare myself to other human beings.
Whenever I try and get work done, I oftenly feel like its not enough or &amp;ldquo;not good enough&amp;rdquo; and sometimes dont even start or quit early on when I dont like something although whenever II am good at something or like the subject I get work done very easily.
In certain periods of times I have frequent suicidal thoughts, or murderous thoughts where I imagine myself traumatizing or seriously injuring a big group of people wanting to be freed from myself and my thoughts, I sometimes think about suicide in these periods, although not often planning on doing so.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
